<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <!-- Data Formats Fragment -->
    <string name="data_formats">Data formats</string>
    <string name="data_formats_date_and_time">Date &amp; time</string>
    <string name="data_formats_data_redaction_and_truncation">Data redaction and truncation</string>

    <!-- Empty States Fragment -->
    <string name="empty_states">Empty states</string>
    <string name="empty_states_txt">Empty states occur when the regular content of a view can’t be shown. It might be a list which has no items, or a search which returned no results. Although these states aren’t typical, they are important opportunities for good design to avoid user disappointment or confusion.
        \n\nIf content cannot be displayed because of a system failure, see <a href="/design/spec/patterns/errors.html#errors-app-errors">app errors</a>.
    </string>

    <!-- Errors Fragment -->
    <string name="errors">Errors</string>
    <string name="errors_txt">Errors occur when an app fails to complete an expected action.</string>
    <string name="errors_user_input_errors">User input errors</string>
    <string name="errors_app_errors">App errors</string>
    <string name="errors_incompatible_state_errors">Incompatible state errors</string>

    <!-- Gestures Fragment -->
    <string name="gestures">Gestures</string>
    <string name="gestures_txt">Gestures are divided into <strong>Touch Mechanics</strong> (what your fingers do on the screen) and <strong>Touch Activities</strong> (results of specific gestures).
        \n\nA touch mechanic (such as swipe) may have multiple results (such as enable/disable), depending on the context. A touch activity (zoom in) may be achieved through multiple touch mechanics (pinch open, double touch, etc.).
        \n\nThe <a href="/design/spec/patterns/gestures.html#gestures-drag-swipe-or-fling-details">Drag, Swipe, and Fling</a> touch activities are covered in more detail due to their highly contextual results.
    </string>
    <string name="gestures_touch_mechanics">Touch mechanics</string>
    <string name="gestures_touch_activities">Touch activities</string>
    <string name="gestures_drag_swipe_or_fling_details">Drag, swipe, or fling details</string>

    <!-- Fingerprint Fragment -->
    <string name="fingerprint">Errors</string>
    <string name="fingerprint_txt">Fingerprint detection can be used to unlock a device, sign in to apps, and authenticate purchases with Google Play and some third-party apps.
        \n\nFingerprint is not as secure as a strong PIN or password.
    </string>

    <!-- Launch Screens Fragment -->
    <string name="launch_screens">Launch screens</string>
    <string name="launch_screens_txt">"The launch screen is a user’s first experience of your application."</string>

    <!-- Loading Images Fragment -->
    <string name="loading_images">Loading images</string>
    <string name="loading_images_loading_images">Loading images</string>

    <!-- Navigation Fragment -->
    <string name="navigation">Navigation</string>
    <string name="navigation_txt">Navigation guides users between different parts of your app.
        \n\nYour app\'s structure should be organized according to the content and tasks you want users to see. Focus attention on important destinations by placing them in tabs or side navigation. Alternatively, de-emphasize inessential content by placing it in less prominent locations.
    </string>

    <!-- Navigation Drawer Fragment -->
    <string name="navigation_drawer">Navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_txt">The navigation drawer is a common pattern found in Google apps. The navigation drawer slides in from the left. It follows the keylines and metrics for lists.</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_specs">Specs</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_content">Content</string>

    <!-- Navigational Transitions Fragment -->
    <string name="navigational_transitions">Navigational transitions</string>
    <string name="navigational_transitions_txt">Navigational transitions are movements between states in an app, such as from a high-level view to a detailed view. Most, but not all, transitions are hierarchical in nature.
        \n\nThese moments should reflect the user’s journey through each state of an app appropriately.
    </string>
    <string name="navigational_transitions_parent_to_child">Parent to child</string>
    <string name="navigational_transitions_sibling_to_sibling">Sibling to sibling</string>

    <!-- Notifications Fragment -->
    <string name="notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="notifications_txt">Notifications inform your app’s users about relevant and timely events in your app. You can create notifications to draw attention to messages from friends, alert a commuter to traffic slowdowns, show the progress of a new app being installed, and more.
        \n\nNotifications should be synced to all of a user’s devices.
    </string>

    <!-- Permissions Fragment -->
    <string name="permissions">Permissions</string>
    <string name="permissions_txt">Permission requests should be simple, transparent, and understandable. When requesting access, apps should ensure that either the feature itself or an explanation provided makes it clear why a permission is needed.</string>

    <!-- Scrolling Techniques Fragment -->
    <string name="scrolling_techniques">Scrolling techniques</string>
    <string name="scrolling_techniques_scrolling">Scrolling</string>

    <!-- Search Fragment -->
    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="search_in_app_search">In-app search</string>

    <!-- Selection Fragment -->
    <string name="selection">Selection</string>
    <string name="selection_txt">Selection includes the gestures and visual cues that enable user choices.</string>
    <string name="selection_item_selection">Item selection</string>
    <string name="selection_text_selection">Text selection</string>

    <!-- Settings Fragment -->
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="settings_txt">Application settings let users indicate their preferences for how an app or service should behave.</string>
    <string name="settings_flow_and_structure">Flow &amp; structure</string>
    <string name="settings_writing_guidelines">Writing guidelines</string>

    <!-- Swipe to Refresh Fragment -->
    <string name="swipe_to_refresh">Swipe to refresh</string>
    <string name="swipe_to_refresh_swipe_to_refresh">Swipe to refresh</string>

</resources>