<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <!-- Accessibility Fragment -->
    <string name="fragment_accessibility">Accessibility</string>
    <string name="fragment_accessibility_txt">A product is accessible when all people — regardless of ability — can navigate it, understand it, and use it to achieve their goals. A truly successful product is accessible to the widest possible audience.
        \n\nThese general guidelines are a good starting point for designers who want to learn about accessibility. Designing fully accessible products is a complex topic that requires in-depth study. For more info, visit the Google accessibility site.
        \n\nTo ensure that your product is usable for users with disabilities, consider how users will interact with your product using assistive technologies. Imagine using your product in the following ways:
        \n\n• Without sound
        \n• Without color
        \n• With the high contrast mode enabled
        \n• With the screen magnified
        \n• With a screen reader (no visible screen)
        \n• With voice control only
        \n• With a combination of the above
    </string>
    <string name="fragment_accessibility_navigation">Navigation</string>
    <string name="fragment_accessibility_readability">Readability</string>
    <string name="fragment_accessibility_guidance_and_feedback">Guidance and feedback</string>

    <!-- Bidirectionality Fragment -->
    <string name="fragment_bidirectionality">Bidirectionality</string>
    <string name="fragment_bidirectionality_txt">A well-designed app can be easily localized for language scripts that are written and read from left-to-right (LTR), such as English, and for <i>bidirectional</i> language scripts.
        \n\nIn bidirectional scripts, text is written and read from right-to-left, but numbers and embedded words from LTR languages, such as non-localized names, are written left-to-right (LTR). Bidirectional scripts include Arabic, Hebrew, and Persian.
        \n\nBidirectionality affects not only the layout of text and UI elements but also iconography. This section provides basic, high-level information about how to consider bidirectionality in design.
    </string>
    <string name="fragment_bidirectionality_ui_mirroring_overview">UI mirroring overview</string>
    <string name="fragment_bidirectionality_rtl_mirroring_guidelines">RTL mirroring guidelines</string>
    <string name="fragment_bidirectionality_other_localization_considerations">Other localization considerations</string>

</resources>