<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <!-- Authentic Motion Fragment -->
    <string name="fragment_authentic_motion">Authentic motion</string>
    <string name="fragment_authentic_motion_txt">Just as the shape of an object indicates how it might behave, watching an object move demonstrates whether it’s light or heavy, flexible or rigid, small or large. In the world of material design, motion describes spatial relationships, functionality, and intention with beauty and fluidity.</string>
    <string name="fragment_authentic_motion_mass_and_weight">Mass and weight</string>

    <!-- Authentic Motion Fragment -->
    <string name="fragment_responsive_interaction">Responsive interaction</string>
    <string name="fragment_responsive_interaction_txt">Apps that practice responsive interaction produce timely, logical, and delightful screen reactions for their users. Each interaction is thoughtful, perhaps whimsical, but never distracting. Responsive interaction encourages deeper exploration of an app. What will happen if I touch this screen? And then this icon?</string>
    <string name="fragment_responsive_interaction_user_input">User input</string>
    <string name="fragment_responsive_interaction_surface_reaction">Surface reaction</string>
    <string name="fragment_responsive_interaction_material_response">Material response</string>
    <string name="fragment_responsive_interaction_radial_action">Radial action</string>

    <!-- Meaningful Transitions Fragment -->
    <string name="fragment_meaningful_transitions">Meaningful transitions</string>
    <string name="fragment_meaningful_transitions_txt">Motion design can effectively guide the user’s attention in ways that both inform and delight. Use motion to smoothly transport users between navigational contexts, explain changes in the arrangement of elements on a screen, and reinforce element hierarchy.</string>
    <string name="fragment_meaningful_transitions_visual_continuity">Visual continuity</string>
    <string name="fragment_meaningful_transitions_hierarchical_timing">Hierarchical timing</string>
    <string name="fragment_meaningful_transitions_consistent_choreography">Consistent choreography</string>

    <!-- Delightful Details Fragment -->
    <string name="fragment_delightful_details">Delightful details</string>
    <string name="fragment_delightful_details_txt">Animation can exist within all components of an app and at all scales, from finely detailed icons to key transitions and actions. All elements work together to construct a seamless experience and a beautiful, functional app.
        \n\nThe most basic use of animation is in transitions, but an app can truly delight a user when animation is used in ways beyond the obvious. A menu icon that becomes an arrow or playback controls that smoothly change from one to the other serve dual functions: to inform the user and to imbue your app with a moment of wonder and a sense of superb craftsmanship. Users do notice such small details.
    </string>

</resources>